http://www.birdandcage.com/privacy.html

| Home | Cages | Stands | Accessories | Playstations | Privacy & Policies | About Us | Links | Questions | Search |
Policies & Privacy Statement
| Documents | Disclaimer | Limitation of Liability | Defective or Damaged Goods | Cancellation & Returns | Offsite Links | Promotions | Privacy Statement | Catalogs |
Shipping
We offer free shipping in the continental US on every order worth $25 or more.
Orders under $25 are subject to a handling fee of $5.95.
If you live elsewhere and wish to place an order, please contact us for a shipping quote.
Documents
Permission to use Documents from this server ("Server") is granted by THE BIRD AND CAGE CO. ("THE BIRD AND CAGE CO."), provided that (1) the below copyright notice appears in all copies and that both the copyright notice and this permission notice appear, (2) use of such Documents from this Server is for informational and non-commercial or personal use only and will not be copied or posted on any network computer or broadcast in any media, and (3) no modifications of any Documents are made. Use for any unauthorized purpose is expressly prohibited by law, and may result in severe civil and criminal penalties. Violators will be prosecuted to the maximum extent possible.
Documents specified above do not include the design or layout of this Web site. Elements of this Web site are protected by trade dress and other laws and may not be copied or imitated in whole or in part. No logo, graphic, sound or image from this Web site may be copied or retransmitted unless expressly permitted by THE BIRD AND CAGE CO.
Disclaimer
While BirdandCage.com uses reasonable efforts to include accurate and up-to-date information on this Web site, THE BIRD AND CAGE CO. makes no warranties or representations as to its accuracy. THE BIRD AND CAGE CO. assumes no liability or responsibility for any typographical or other errors or omissions in the content on this site. In the event that a product is listed at an incorrect price or with other incorrect information due to a typographical or other error, THE BIRD AND CAGE CO. shall have the right to refuse or cancel any orders placed for the product listed incorrectly.
THE BIRD AND CAGE CO. shall have the right to refuse or cancel any such orders whether or not the order has been confirmed and/or your credit card has been charged. If your credit card has already been charged for the purchase and your order is canceled, THE BIRD AND CAGE CO. shall issue a credit to your credit card account in the amount of the charge. If a product offered by THE BIRD AND CAGE CO. is not as described, your sole remedy is to return it to THE BIRD AND CAGE CO. for a refund.
Limitation of Liability
THE BIRD AND CAGE CO. AND/OR ITS RESPECTIVE SUPPLIERS MAKE NO REPRESENTATIONS ABOUT THE SUITABILITY OF THE INFORMATION CONTAINED IN THE DOCUMENTS AND RELATED GRAPHICS ON THIS SERVER FOR ANY PURPOSE. ALL SUCH DOCUMENTS AND RELATED GRAPHICS ARE PROVIDED "AS IS" WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND AND ARE SUBJECT TO CHANGE WITHOUT NOTICE. THE ENTIRE RISK ARISING OUT OF THEIR USE REMAINS WITH THE RECIPIENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE BIRD AND CAGE CO. AND/OR ITS RESPECTIVE SUPPLIERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, CONSEQUENTIAL, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, PUNITIVE OR OTHER DAMAGES WHATSOEVER (INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION, DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF BUSINESS PROFITS, BUSINESS INTERRUPTION, OR LOSS OF BUSINESS INFORMATION), EVEN IF THE BIRD AND CAGE CO. HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.
Defective or Damaged Merchandise
If merchandise is damaged in shipping call us first at (281) 420-2201 within three (3) business days of the date of delivery of the damaged goods. The Bird & Cage Co. will contact the shipping company and arrange for the return. In the event an item is defective, call The Bird & Cage Co. within three business days of the date of delivery and we will correct the problem.
Cancellation & Returns
All returns must be authorized by The Bird & Cage Co. or they will not be accepted. Shipping fees are not refundable unless you are returning defective merchandise or merchandise The Bird & Cage Co. has sent in error. ALL returned merchandise must include all original boxes and parts. If a bird has been housed in the cage for any period of time the cage is not returnable. Returns will be subject to a 25% restocking fee plus freight charges.
No returns on sale items.
THE BIRD AND CAGE CO. AND/OR ITS RESPECTIVE SUPPLIERS ASSUME NO LIABILITY IN THE EVENT OF LOST OR DAMAGE SHIPMENTS BEYOND REPLACMENT VALUE OF THE ITEM OR ITEMS EITHER LOST OR DAMAGED. THE BIRD AND CAGE CO. AND/OR ITS RESPECTIVE SUPPLIERS ARE NOT LIABLE FOR ANY OR ALL SHIPPING COSTS.
Links to Third-Party Sites
LINKED SITES ARE NOT UNDER THE CONTROL OF THE BIRD AND CAGE CO. AND THE BIRD AND CAGE CO. IS NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR THE CONTENTS OF ANY LINKED SITE OR ANY LINK CONTAINED IN A LINKED SITE. THE BIRD AND CAGE CO. PROVIDES LINKS TO YOU ONLY AS A CONVENIENCE, AND THE INCLUSION OF ANY LINK DOES NOT IMPLY ENDORSEMENT BY THE BIRD AND CAGE CO. OF THE SITE.
Promotions
All promotions are subject to availability and inventory. THE BIRD AND CAGE CO. reserves the right to change, alter, or cancel promotions at any time without notice.
Privacy Statement
THE BIRD AND CAGE CO. considers the responsible use of personal information to be a critical element in enabling the Internet to reach its potential as a serious tool for personal and professional activities. As the Internet changes our lives in a number of ways, THE BIRD AND CAGE CO. is committed to respecting your privacy.
In general, you can visit www.Birdandcage.com without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself.
There are times, however, when we may need information from you, such as your name, home or business address and e-mail address. THE BIRD AND CAGE CO. will seek to let you know before we collect any personal information from you over the Internet. Some examples of when we may need information are if you choose to purchase a product directly from THE BIRD AND CAGE CO. Web site.
When you choose to give us personal information over the Internet that we or our business partners may request, THE BIRD AND CAGE CO. will endeavor to let you know how we will use this information. THE BIRD AND CAGE CO. will also seek to take appropriate steps to protect the information you share with us, including using appropriate technology for credit card data used in electronic commerce transactions.
If you have any questions or comments about our privacy practices, please contact us by sending an email to ew@Birdandcage.com.
Catalogs
Sorry, we do not have any printed catalogs. In order to keep our prices low, we have chosen to sell through our website, instead of the expense of a printed catalog. This, in return, is ecologically sound and we are saving trees!
| Bird Cages | Cage Stands | Toys & Accessories | Playstations |
| Privacy & Policies | About Us | Links | Questions | Site Map |
updated May 15, 2004
Search
The Web
Bird & Cage
Copyright © 2004 by Bird & Cage Co.
All rights reserved
| Home | Cages | Stands | Accessories | Playstations | Privacy & Policies | About Us | Links | Questions | Search |
